You are given an arithmetic expression containing n real numbers and n − 1 operators, each
either + or ×. Your goal is to perform the operations in an order that maximizes the value of
the expression. That is, insert n − 1 pairs of parentheses into the expression so that its value
is maximized.

For example:

• For the expression 6 × 3 + 2 × 5, the optimal ordering is to add the middle numbers
first, then perform the multiplications: ((6 × (3 + 2)) × 5) = 150.

• For the expression 0.1×0.1+0.1, the optimal ordering is to perform the multiplication
first, then the addition: ((0.1 × 0.1) + 0.1) = 0.11.

• For the expression (−3) × 3 + 3, the optimal ordering is ((−3) × 3) + 3) = −6.